The Guide to the John Canemaker Animation Collection 1903-2012 (Bulk 1970-2000) MSS 040
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 2012 - Oversize: Series VI - Major Projects
  - Subseries G: "Two Guys Named Joe"
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, Joe Grant - Caricatures c. 1920/1930's, Joe Ranft - Drawings [3 of 4], undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, Joe Grant - Caricatures c. 1920/1930's, Joe Ranft - Drawings [4 of 4], undated (Box 8, Folder 25)